Charles, you have finally
lost your senses
This venture is impossible.
For some.
Gentlemen, the only way to achieve the
impossible is to think that it is possible.
That kind of thinking could ruin you
I'm willing to take that chance.
Imagine a trading post
in Rangoon! Bangkok, Jakarta!
The nightmare again?
I won't be long
I'm falling
Down a dark hole.
Then I see strange creatures.
What kind of creatures?
There's a dodo bird,
a rabbit in a waist coat
and a smiling cat
I did not know cats could smile.
Neither did I.
And there is a blue caterpillar.
A blue caterpillar?
Do you think I've gone round the bend?
I'm afraid so.
You're mad, bonkers, off your head
But I'll tell you a secret.
All the best people are.
It's only a dream, Alice,
nothing can harm you there.
But if you get too frightened,
You can always wake up.
Like this
Must we go?
I doubt he'll notice
if we never arrive
He will notice
Where 's your corset?
- And no stockings.
- I'm against them.
But you are not properly dressed
Who is to say what is "proper"?
What if it was agreed that "proper"was wearing
a codfish on your head, would you wear it?
Alice ...
For me, a corset is like a codfish
Please, not today.
Father would have laughed.
I'm sorry.
I'm tired.
I didn't sleep well last night.
Did you have bad dreams again?
Only one.
It's always the same, ever since I can remember
Do you think that's normal?
Don't most people have different dreams?
I don't know.
There.
You're beautiful.
Now, can you mange to smile?
At last.
We thought you'd never arrive
Alice, Hamish is waiting to dance with you .
Go.
You do realize it's well past 4??
Now everything I've been rushed through
- I'm sorry.
- Nevermind.
Forgive my wife. She been planning
this affair for over 20 years.
If only Charles were here.
My condolences
I think off your husband often.
He was truly a man of vision
I hope you do not think I've taken
advantage of your misfortunes
Of course not.
I'm pleased that you've purchased the company.
I was a fool for not investing in his mad venture
when I had the chance
Charles thought the same too
Hamish, do you ever get tired of quadrille?
On the contrary.
I find it envigorating
Do I amuse you?
No.
I had a sudden vision. Off all the ladies
in trousers and the men wearing dresses
It would be best to keep your visons to yourself.
When in doubt, remain silent.
Pardon us, sir.
Ms. Kingsley is distracted today.
- Where is your head?
- I was wondering what it would be like to fly.
Why would spend your time thinking About
such an impossible thing?
Why wouldn't I?
My father said he sometimes believed
in six impossible things
before breakfast.
Alice, meet me at the Gazebo
in precisely ten minutes.
We have a secret to tell you.
If you're telling me,
then it's not much of a secret
- Perhaps we shouldn't.
- We've decided we should.
- If you tell us, we won't be surprised.
- Will you be surprised?
Not if you tell me
But now you've brought it up,
you have to
- No, we don't
- In fact, we won't
I wonder if your mother knows that
you two swim naked into Havershim pond.
- You wouldn't.
- Oh, but I would
There's your mother right now
Hamish is going to ask for your hand.
You've ruined the surprise.
Oh, I could strangle them!
Everyone of us went through so much trouble
to keep it a secret
Does everyone know?
That's why they have all come.
This is your engagement party.
Hamish will ask you under the gazebo
When you say "yes" ...
But I don't know if I want to marry Hamish.
Who then?
You won't do better than a lord.
You'll soon be 20, Alice.
That pretty face won't last forever.
You don't want to end up like aunt Imogen.
You don't want to be a burden
for mother, do you?
No.
So, you'll marry Hamish.
You'll be as happy as I am with
Lowell and you live will be perfect
It's already decided.
Alice, dear
I'll leave you to it.
Shall we take a leisurely stroll through
the garden, just you and me ?
Do you know what I've always dreaded?
The decline of teh artistocracy ?
Ugly grandchildren.
But you are lovely.
You are bound to produce little...
Imbeciles!
The gardeners planted white roses
when i specifically asked for red.
You could always paint the roses red
What an odd thing to say
You should know that my son
has extremely delicate digestion.
- Did you see that?
- See what?
- It was a rabbit, I think
- Nasty things
I'd enjoy setting the dogs on them
If you serve Hamish the wrong foods,
he could get a blockage.
- Did you see it that time?
- See what?
- The rabbit!
- Don't shout!
Now pay attention.
Hamish said you were easily distracted.
What was I saying?
Hamish was a blockage.
I couldn't be more interested,
but you'll have to excuse me
Aunt Imogen!
I think I'm going mad.
I keep seeing a rabbit in a waist coat
I can't be bothered with you fancy rabbit now
I'm waiting for my fiancee.
Your have a fiancee?
There! Did you see it?
He's a prince.
But alas he can not marry me
unless he renounces his throne.
- It's tragic, isn't it?
- Very.
Lowell?
Alice! We were just ...
Kathy is an old friend.
I can see you are very close.
You won't mention this to your sister,
will you?
I don't know.
I'm confused.
I need time to think
Well, think About Margaret.
She'd never trust me again
- You don't want to ruin her marriage, do you?
- Me?
But I'm not the one who is sneaking around her back...
Here you are.
- Alice Kingsley ...
- Hamish.
- What is it?
- You have a caterpillar on his shoulder.
Ughh!
You'll want to wash that finger.
Alice Kingsley ...
Will you be my wife?
Well ...
Everyone expects me to
And, you are a Lord.
My fast won't last and
I don't want to end up like..
But this is happening so quickly, I...
I think I ...
I need a moment.
Hi!
DRINK ME
It's only a dream.
You'd say she'd remember all
this from the first time.
You have brought the wrong Alice.
She is the right one.
I'm certain off it.
EAT ME
- She´s the wrong Alice!
- Give her a chance.
Curious and curiouser
I told you she´s the right Alice
- I am not convinced.
- How is that for gratitude?
I was out there for weeks,
trailing one Alice after the next
I was almost eaten
by other animals.
Can you imagine ...
They go About entirely unclothed
And they do there shukm in public,
I had to avert my eyes
-You do not look anything like us Alice!
That´s because she the wrong Alice!
- If she was, she might be.
- But if she isn´t, she ain´t
- But if she was so, she would be.
- But she isn´t, No how!
How can I be the wrong Alice
when this is my dream?
And who are you if i might ask?
Oh, I am Tweedlee and he's Tweedledum.
Come cherry wise,
I am Tweedledum and he is Teweedlee.
- We should consult Absolum.
- Exactly!
- Absolem will know who she is.
- Alice, come on dear.
- It´s not being your turn, it´s so unfair, leave off her!
- Let go!
- Are they always this way?
- It's a family trade.
You can a both escort her
- Who is this Absolem?
- He´s wise. He´s Absolute ...
He´s Absolute!
Who are you?
- Absolem!
- You´re not Absolem. I'm Absolem.
The question is ...
Who are you?
- Alice.
- We shall see.
What do you mean by that?
I ought to know who i am
Yes, you ought. Stupid girl!
Unroll The Oraculum.
The Oraculum, being the
calendrical compemdium of Underland
- It´s a calender.
- Compendium.
It tells of each and every day
since the beginning
Today is Gribling day,
in the time of the Red Queen
Show her the FrAbjous Day.
Yes, FrAbjous, being the day you´ll
slay the JAbberwocky
Sorry?
Slay the what?
That being you there with the
Vorpal sword.
No other swords can kill
JAbberwocky's. No how.
If it ain´t Vorpal, it ain´t dead
- That´s not me.
- I know!
Resolve this for us, Absolem.
Is she the right Alice?
Not hardly.
I told ya!
- I said so
Contrary wise,
you said she might be.
No, you said she would be if
she was.
Little Impostor! Pretending to be Alice!
She should be ashamed!
- I was so certain of you.
- I´m sorry, I don´t mean to be the wrong Alice!
Wait.
This is my dream.
I am going to wake up now and
you will all disappear.
That´s odd
Pinching usually does the trick
- I could stick you if that would help?
- It might actually, thank you.
My pleasure!
Bandersnatch!
Wait.
It is only a dream.
Nothing could hurt me.
- What is she doing?
- He can´t hurt me, he can´t hurt me ...
Run, you great love!
SNUD and QUEAST
- This way!
- East to QUEAST.
No! South to SNUD!
Someone has stolen three of my tarts!
- Did You steal them?
- No, Your Majesty.
- Did You?
- Did You steal them?
- No, Your Majesty.
- Did you steal my tart?
- No, Your Majesty ...
It´s cranberry juice.
- I was so hungry! I did not mean to ...
- Off with his head!
My family! No, please, please don´t!
I have little ones to look after!
Go to his house
and collect the little ones.
I like frog eggs on toast almost
as much as I like caviar.
Yes, your Majesty
Drink.
Majesty.
Ilosovic Stayne
Where have you been lurking?
Majesty ...
I have found the Oraculum
That? Looks so ordinary
for an Oraculum.
Look here. FrAbjous Day.
I´d know that tangled mess of hair anywhere.
Is it Alice?
I believe it is.
What is she doing with my darling JAbberwocky?
She appears to be slating it
She killed my JAbberbAbywocky?
Not yet. But it will happen
if we don´t stop her.
Find Alice, Stayne.
Find her!
Find the scent of human girl
and earn your freedom.
For my wife and pups as well?
Everyone will go home.
Dogs will believe anything.
I looks like you ran afoul of
something with wicked claws
- I must be still dreaming ...
- What did that to you?
- A "bender" or "bandips" ...
- A Bandersnatch?
- Well, I´d better have a look.
- What are you doing?
It needs to by purified by someone
with evaporating skills
or it will fester and putrify
I´d rather you didn´t.
I´ll be fine as soon as I wake up.
At least let me bind it for you
- What do you call yourself?
- Alice.
THE Alice?
There has been some debate About that
I never get involved in politics.
You´d best be on your way.
What way? All I want to do
is wake from this dream.
Fine. I´ll take you to the Hare
and the Hatter, but that´s the end of it
Coming.
Watch what you´re doing!
It´s you!
No it´s not.
The Twisp brought us the wrong Alice
- Its the wrong Alice?
- It's Absolutely Alice.
You're Absolutely Alice.
I´d know you anywhere.
I´d know him anywhere!
Well, as you can see,
we´re still having tea.
And it´s all because I was obliged
to kill time waiting for your return.
You´re terribly late, you know
Naughty!
Well anyway, time to came quite offended
has stopped all together. Not a tick off a finger
- Cup.
- Time can be funny in dreams.
Yes, yes, of course,
but now you're back, you see.
- And we need to get on to the FrAbjous Day.
- FrAbjous Day!
I´ve been investigating things that begin with
the letter "M".
Have you any idea why a raven is
like a writing desk?
- "Downal wyth Bluddy Behg Hid
"!
- What?
"Down with the Bloody Big Head"
Bloody Big Head, being The Red Queen
Come, come we simply must commit to the slaying
in such
Therefore, is it high time to forgive and forget
or forgive and forgive
whichever comes first, or is in any case
the most convenient, I´m waiting.
It´s ticking, it´s ticking again
All this talk of blood and slaying has
put me off my tea
The entire world is falling to ruin and
poor Chester is off his tea.
What happened that day was not... my fault
Oh, dear
Your were out and then
to save your own skin
You gutless Scottisch pelgrim juggling
slurking urpal slackush scrum Barlemot
Hatter!
Thank you.
I´m fine
What wrong with you, Tarrant?
You used to be the light of the party.
You used to do the best Futterwacken
in all of WitzEnd
Futter what?
It's a dance.
One day, FrAbjous Day,
when the White Queen once again
wears the crown
On that day I shall Futterwacken ...
vigorously.
Oh no!
- The Knave
- Goodbye.
Drink this quickly.
Oh, dear
Let me out!
Well!
If it's not my favorite trio of lunatics.
Would you like to join us?
You´re all late for tea!
I´m looking the girl
called ... Alice.
Speaking of the Queen,
Here's a little song we used
to sing in her honour.
Twinkle, twinkle little red
how I wonder where you´re at
If you´re hiding her,
you´ll lose your heads.
Already lost them.
All together noW!
Up Above the world you fly,
like a tea tray in the sky
Twinkle, twinkle little
Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle,twinkle
Don´t be bloody beggin´!
Would you like some tea?
Follow the blood hound
- Sugar?
- Yes, please.
- You're all mad !
- Thanks very much.
Pass the scones, please.
Try this one for size.
I like it!
Good thing the blood hound is one
of us, or you´d be...
What do they want with me?
Best take her to the
White Queen, she´d be safe there!
Spoon.
- Your carriage, m'lady.
- The Hat ?
Of course!
Anyone can go by horse
or rail
But the Absolute best way to travel
is by hat
Have i made a rhyme?
I love travelling by hat!
Mally,just Alice, please
Fairfallen all!
Twas brillig, and the slithy toves
Did gyre and gimble in the wAb
All mimsy were the borogoves
And the mome raths outgrAbe
Sorry, what was that ?
What was what?
The JAbberwock with eyes of flame,
jaws that bite and claws that catch
Beware of the Jubjub bird,my son
The frumnious Bandersnatch!.
He took his Vorpal sword in hand
The Vorpal blade went snicker-snack
He left it dead, and with its head
He went galumphing back
It's all About you, you know
I'm not slaying anything , I don't slay,
so put it out of you mind!
Mind?
Wait! you can't leave me here!
You don't slay?
Do you have any idea what
the Red Queen has done?
You don't slay?
I couldn't if I wanted to
You're not the same as you were before
You were much more, muchier
You lost your muchness
"My muchness?
In there, something's missing
Tell me what Red Queen has done
It is not a pretty story.
Tell me anyway.
It was here
I was the Hatter to the
White Queen at the time
Hatter ...
Hatter!
I'm fine.
Are you?
Did you hear that?
I'm certain I heard something.
What?
Red Knave
Go south to Trottler's Bottom
The White Queen's castle is just beyond.
Hold on tightly.
Done it with the Bloody Red Queen!
You were supposed to lead them away!
The Hatter trusted you!
They have my wife and pups
- What is your name?
- Bayard.
Sit!
Would your name be Alice,
by any chance?
Yes, but I'm not the one that
everybody is talking About
The Hatter would have given himself
up just for any Alice.
Where did they take him?
To the Red Queen's Castle,
it's Salazen Grum.
We're going to rescue him.
That is not foretold
I don't care!
He wouldn't be there,
if I weren't for me
The FrAbjous day is almost upon us.
You must prepare to meet the JAbberwocky.
From the moment I fell down that rabbit hole,
I have been told what I must do and who I must be.
I've been shrunk, stretched, scratched and
stuffed into a teapot.
I've been accused of being Alice and of
not being Alice, but this is my dream.
I'll decide where it goes from here!
If you diverge from the path...
I make the path!
Take me to Salazen Grum, Bayard,
and don´t forget the hat.
There´s only one way across
I´ve lost my muchness, have I?
Bayard! Hat!
Your Majesty.
So Sorry
Splendid shot!
Where's my ball?
Page!
Yes, Your Majesty.
I want to help you
Well, If it isn´t the wrong Alice
What brings you here?
I´ve come to rescue the Hatter.
You won´t be rescuing anyone being the
size of a jarbel.
Do you have any more of that cake
that made me grow before?
"Upelkuchen?
Actually, i might have some left
Not all of it!
Oh, no stop!
Oh no, don´t do that!
Oh dear,
And what is this?
It´s a who, Majesty.
This is...humm...
Humm?
From Urnbradge.
What happened to your clothes?
I outgrew them.
I´ve been growing an afwul lot lately
I tower over everyone in Urnbradge.
They laugh at me.
So I´ve come to you,
hoping you might understand what it´s like.
My dear girl, anyone with a head
that large is welcome in my court.
Someone find us some clothes!
Use curtains, if you must,
but clothed this enormous girl
I need a pig here!
I love a warm pig belly for
my aching feet
Would you like one, Humm?
- No, thank you.
- Sit!
Sit!
Go away!
Where are my fat boys?
You must meet them.
Fat Boys!
There they are.
Aren´t they adorAble?
They have the oddest way of speaking.
Speak, boys. Amuse us.
Speak!
- Is that being..
- No,no, it is not a bit, no
I´m sure it was, I believe it´s so
No it ain´t, son. No how
I love my Fat Boys
Now, get out!
And.. who is this
lovely creature?
- Humm. My new favorite.
- Does she have a name?
Humm.
I believe your name has slipped the Queen´s mind.
Her name is Humm, Idiot!
From Urnbradge.
Any luck with the prisoner?
He´s stubborn.
Or too soft.
Bring him!
We know Alice has returned to Underland,
do you know where she is?
I´ve been considering things that
begin with the letter M
Moron
Mutiny, Murder, Malice
We´re looking for an A word now
Where is Alice?
I would not know.
What if I take off your head?
Will you know then?
Stop it.
What a regrettAbly large head you have
I would very much like to hat it.
- Hat it?
- Yes.
I used to have the White Queen you know
Wasn´t very much to work with, poor dear
Her head is so small
It´s tiny.
It´s a pimple of a head
What I could do with this monument,
with this all..
with this magnificently heroic globe
What could you do?
Unbind him, Stayne.
How can he work, when his hands
are bound?
Well then...
Shall it be a bond or a bowlock?
Or something for the boudoir?
Hatter!
Leave us!
Have you been speaking with him?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Perhaps a bit more kindly
Would you all excuse me for a moment?
Thank you.
- What news, Bayard?
- Alice has returned to Underland.
Where is she now?
In Salazin Grum.
Forgive me, I allowed her to
divert from her destined path.
That is exactly where she´ll
will find the Volpen Sword
We have our champion. Rest now.
You have done well!
Have you seen a hat ´round here?
You must find Alice, Stayne.
Without JAbberwocky, my sister´s followers
will shortly rise against me
My ugly little sister
Why do they adore her, but not me?
I can not fadden it
You are far superior in all ways
I know. But Moana can have
anyone fall in love with her.
Men.
Women.
Even the furniture.
Even the.. King?
I had to do it.
He would have left me
Majesty ...
It is not better to be feared
than be loved?
Not certain anymore
Let her have them rebel
I don´t need them.
I have you.
They are wonderful.
You must let me try one on
It's good to be working
with my trade again
It's just a pity you have to
make them for her
What does the hatter with mean?
Hatter!
Do you have any idea why a raven is
like a writing desk?
I'm frightened, Alice.
I don´t like it in here.
It's terribly crowded.
Have I gone mad?
Afraid so.
You´re entirely bonkers
But I´ll tell you a secret.
All the best people are.
Here.
That´s better.
You look yourself again.
Hat man? Where are my hats
I am no a patient person
I´m told she has the Vorpal sword hidden in the castle.
The rabbit will help you.
Find it,Alice. Take it to the White Queen.
We´ll go to the White Queen together.
Why is it, you´re always too smal or too tall?
- Tweedles
- Alice, how are you doing, kid?
- Where is the rabbit?
- How is it, you´re being so great big?
She ain´t great big.
This is how she normal is
I'm sure she is smaller when we met
No, she drink "pishsalver" to get
through the door, recall it?
- Where is the rabbit?
- There.
- What are you doing here?
- I´m rescuing The Hatter.
I am rescuing The Hatter!
He told me that the Vorpal sword
is hidden in the castle.
Help me find it!
I don´t take orders from big,
clumpsy, galumphing...
- What is it, Big Twisp?
- I know where the sword is.
The sword is hidden inside.
Be careful, Alice.
I´m not going in there!
Look what that thing did to my arm!
Dear Oh dear,
Why haven´t you mentioned this?
It wasn´t this bad before
Hatter!
Where are you?
Mallymkun.
Do you still have the
Bandersnatch's eye ?
Right here.
- I need it.
- Come and get it.
Give it back!
I like you Humm
I like large things ...
Get away from me!
I have your eye.
No.
- You look stunning in that hat.
- Yes. Next!
Your Majesty has never looked
better!
Another!
I don´t wish to alarm you,but I smell as
though you might have dropped something.
Don´t mind him, he´s mad
Come along!
Stayne!
I suppose that make us even now
Humm forced herself on me. I told her
my heart belongs to you
She´s obsessed with me.
Off with the head!
Stand back, Mallymkun.
How is this for muchness?
It mustn´t be used for anything...
Arrested that girl
for unlawful seduction!
Hatter!
- Take it to the White Queen!
- I´m not leaving without you!
Go!
Run...
Alice!
Alice.
Run!
Seize her!
Alice ...
Of course
Why didn´t I see it?
But it has been such a long time
you was such a little tike then
Give me the sword.
- Stay back.
- The queen will be so pleased
Shee will take great pleasure
in cutting off your head.
Ho! Alice!
Bayard!
To Marmoreal!
Majesty ...
Alice has escaped.
On ... the Bandersnatch.
With ... the Vorpal sword.
How could you let it happen?
I might have underestimated her
But we have her conspirators.
The Hatter and a door mouse.
Off with their heads!
- Welcome to Marmoreal.
- I believe this belongs to you.
The Vorpal sword is home again
The Armor is complete
Now all we need is a champion
You're a little taller than
I thought you'd be
Blame it on too much Upelkuchen.
Come with me.
Is the March Hare here?
It could use some salt.
Yes, that´s great
Be sure About it, we need
A pinch of worm fat
Buttered fingers.
My sister prefered to study
"Dominion Of The Living Things"
- Tell me, how did she seem to you?
- Perfectly horrid
- And... her head?
- Bulbous
I think she might have some growth
in there, something pressing on her brain
Three coins from a dead man´s pocket
Two tea spoons of "wishful thinking".
You can´t iamgine the things that
go on in that place
Yes, I can.
But when a champion steps
forward to slay the JAbberwocky,
the people will rise against her.
That should do it!
Blow.
- Feeling better?
- Much Thank you.
There´s someone here who´d like
to speak with you
- Absolem!
- Who are you?
I thought we´d settled this
I'm Alice, but not that one
How do you know?
You´ve said so yourself
I said you were hardly Alice,
but you´re much more her now.
In fact, you are almost Alice.
Even so, I could not slay the
JAbberwocky
if my life depended on it
It will
So suggest you keep the Vorpal Sword
hand for when the FrAbjous Day arrives
You seem so real.
Sometimes I forget that this is all a dream.
Will you stop doing that?
I have always admired
that hat.
Hello, Chess.
Since you wouldn´t be needing it anymore
would you consider begrieving it to me
How dare you?
It is an formal execution.
I would like to look my best, you know
It´s a pity About all this
I was looking forward to seeing
you Futterwacken
I was ready good at it, was I not?
I really DO love that hat.
I´d wear to all the finest occasions.
I love a morning execution
Don´t you?
Yes, Your Majesty.
- I would like to keep it on.
- Suit yourself
As long as I can get at your neck
I´m right here, behind ya
- Off with his head!
- I can´t watch.
Good morning, everyone.
Chess, you dog!
Madam?
You are being hanously bamboozled by these
lick spittled toves you surround yourself with
What is that?
- I´m not the only one Majesty. Look.
- A counterfeit nose. You should be ashamed!
Me? What About that big belly
you´re so proud off?
Liars! Cheats!
Off with their heads!
The Abused and enslaved
in the Red Queen´s court!
All of you, stand up and fight!
Rise up against the Bloody Red Queen!
Downal wyth Bluddy Behg Hid!
Release the Jubjub bird!
You were right, Stayne.
It's far better to be feared than loved.
Come with me! Quick, come!
- Hatter!
- Come on, Melly, quickly! Come on!
Prepare the JAbberwocky for battle.
We're going to visit
my little sister.
I had hope to have a champion by now
Why don´t you slay the
JAbberwocky yourself?
You must have the power.
It is against my vows to harm
any living creature.
We have company.
Have a look, Bayard.
- So happy to see you, I thought they were going to...
- Send me to die, but they didn´t.
And here I am, still in one piece!
I´d rather have died than
never seeing you again
I would regret not seeing you
especially since you are you,
in the proper size. It a great
size, it the right size, it´s..
Hatter.
Where´s your hat.
- Cheshire.
- How´s the arm, love?
- All healed.
- Goodbye, sweet hat
Have you any idea why a raven is
like a writing desk?
Let me think About it.
You know what tomorrow is, don´t you?
FrAbjous Day, how I could forget?
I wish I´d wake up.
You still believe this is
a dream, do you?
Of course
This all coming from my own mind.
Which would mean that I´m not real.
Afraid so.
You're just a figment of my
imagination
I would dream up someone who´s half mad
Yes, yes. But you would have to be´
half mad to dream me up.
I must be then.
I´ll miss you when I wake up.
Who will step forth to be
champion for the White Queen?
That would be I
You have any poor evaporating skills
I should be the one.
I´ll do it
No, me.
No, me!
No other slayer, no how
If it ain´t Alice, it ain´t dead
Alice ...
You cannot live your life
to please others,
The choice must be yours.
Because when you step out to face that creature,
you will step out alone
Nothing was ever accomplished with tears
Absolem?
Why are you upside down?
I´ve come to the end of this life.
You´re going to die?
Transform.
You can´t go. I need our
help, I don´t know what to do.
I can´t help if you don´t even know
who you are, stupid girl.
I´m not stupid!
My name is Alice,
I live in London.
I have a mother named Helen
and a sister named Margaret.
My father was Charles Kingsley.
He had a vision that stretched halfway around
the world and nothing ever stopped him
I am his daughter.
I'm Alice Kingsley.
Alice ... At last!
You are just as dimwitted as
the first time you were here
You called it Wonderland, as I recall
Wonderland.
- What do you call yourself?
- Alice.
THE Alice?
I´ll take you to the Hare
and the Hatter.
She the right one,
I'm certain.
Look at the tAble.
Please, have some tea.
Stupid Girl.
- And what is this?
You would think she would
remember all this from the first time.
It wasn´t a dream at all.
It was a memory.
This place is real!
So are you and so is the Hatter!
And the JAbberwocky
Remember, the Vorpal Sword knows
what it wants
All you have to do, is hold on to it.
Farewell, Alice.
Perhaps I will see you in another life.
Hello, Iracebeth.
Hello ...
Mirana
On this, the FrAbjous day,
The Queens, Red and White shall
send forth their champions
to do battle on their behalf.
Iracy, we don´t have to fight
I know what you´re doing.
You think you can blink
those pretty little eyes
and I´ll melt, just like
mommy and daddy did.
Please.
No!
It's my crown!
I am the eldest!
JAbberwocky!
This is impossible.
Only if you believe it is
"Sometimes I believe as many as six
impossible things before breakfast. "
That´s excellent practice
However, just at the moment,
you really might want to focus on the JAbberwocky
Where 's your champion, sister?
Here.
Hello, Humm.
Six impossible things.
Count them, Alice.
One. There´s a potion that
can make you shrink
Two. A cake that can make you grow.
So, my old foe
We meet on the battlefield, once again
- We've never met.
- Not you, insignificant bearer.
My ancient enemy, the Vorpal one
That´s enough chatter!
Three. Animals can talk.
Four. Alice ...
Cats can disappear.
Five.
There is a place called
Wonderland
Six.
I can slay the JAbberwocky
The Hatter is interfering !
Off with his head!
Off with your head!
Kill her!
We follow you no more,
Bloody Big Head!
How dare you?
Off with his head!
Iracebeth off Crims,
your crimes against Underland
are worthy off death
However,
that is against my vows.
Therefore you will be banished
to the Outlands
No one is to show you any kindness
or ever speak a word to you.
You will not have a friend in
the world ...
Majesty, I hope you bare on me no
ill will
Iracy won´t be alone Stayne
you are to join Iracebeth in banishment
from this day on, until the end of Underland.
Even we have each other.
Majesty, please, kill me!
Please!
But you do not owe your my kindness
- Take off my head!
- You tried to kill me?
- Majesty! Please!
- He tried to kill me!
He tried to kill me!
O FrAbjous Day!
- What is he doing?
- Futterwacken.
The blood of the JAbberwocky.
You have our everlasting gratitude.
And for your efforts
on our behalf ...
- Will this take me home?
- If that is what you choose.
You could stay.
What an idea?
A crazy mad wonderful idea!
But I can´t
They are questions I have to answer
Things I have to do.
I´ll be back again, before you know it
You won´t remember me.
Off course I will.
How could I forget?
Hatter,why is a raven
like a writing desk?
I haven´t the slightest idea
Fairfarren Alice.
She left me standing there
without an answer
A case of nerves, no doubt
- Alice.
- God, lord!
- Are you alright?
- What happened to you?
I fell down a hole
and hit my head.
I'm sorry, Hamish,
I can´t marry you.
You´re not the right man for me.
You´ll always have problems with your digestion.
I love you, Margaret,
but this is my life.
I´ll decide what to do with it.
You're lucky to my sister for
your wife, Lowell.
I know you´ll be good to her.
I'll be watching very closely.
There is no prince, Aunt Imogen
You need to talk to somebody
About these delusions
I happen to like rabbits,
especially white ones.
Do not worry, Mother.
I´ll find something useful to do with my life.
You two remind me of some funny boys
I met in a dream
- You´ve left me out.
- No, I haven´t, sir.
You and I have business to discuss
Shall we speak... in the study
Oh, and one more thing.
My father told me he wanted to expand
his trade routes to Sumatra and Borneo
But I don´t not think he was looking
far enough.
Why not go all the way to China?
It's vast, the culture´s rich
and we have a foothole in Hong Kong.
To be the first to trade with China,
Can you imagine it?
You know, if somebody had said that to me,
I´d have said you´ve lost your senses
But I´ve seen that look before
As you´re not going to be my daughter in law,
Perhaps you´d consider becoming an
apprentice with the company?
Hello, Absolem.