♪♪ [ Chorus ]
♪ Alice in Wonderland ♪
♪ How do you get to Wonderland ♪
♪ Over the hill or underland ♪
♪ Orjust behind the tree ♪
♪ When clouds go rolling by ♪
♪ They roll away
and leave the sky ♪
♪ Where is the land
beyond the isles ♪
♪ That people cannot see ♪
♪ Where can it be ♪
♪ Where do stars go ♪
♪ Where is the crescent moon ♪
♪ They must be somewhere ♪
♪ In the sunny afternoon ♪
♪ Alice in Wonderland ♪
♪ Where is the path
to Wonderland ♪
♪ Over the hill
or here or there ♪
♪ I wonder where ♪♪
" ...And had been of late
much accustomed...
" to usurpation
and conquest.
" Edwin and Morcar,
" the earls of Mercia
and Northumbria,
" declared for him.
" And even Stigand--"
Alice!
Hmm?
I'm listening.
" And even Stigand,
" the Archbishop
of Canterbury,
" agreed to meet
with William...
" and offer him
the crown.
William'
conduct was--"
Alice!
Pay attention to
your history lesson.
How can one
pay attention...
to a book
with no pictures?
There are many good books
in this world...
without pictures.
In this world, perhaps.
But in my world,
the books will be
nothing but pictures.
Your world?
What nonsense.
Nonsense?
That' it, Dinah!
If I had
a world of my own,
everything
would be nonsense.
Nothing would
be what it is.
Everything would
be what it isn't .
What it is,
it wouldn't be,
and what it wouldn't be,
it would.
- You see?
- Meow.
In my world,
you wouldn't say " meow."
You'd say,
"Yes, Miss Alice."
Meow.
But you would.
You'd be
just like people.
And all the other
animals, too.
In my world...
♪ Cats and rabbits ♪
♪ Would reside
in fancy little houses ♪
♪ And be dressed in shoes
and hats and trousers ♪
♪ In a world
of my own ♪
♪ All the flowers ♪
♪ Would have very
extra-special powers ♪
♪ They would sit
and talk to me for hours ♪
♪ When I'm lonely ♪
♪ In a world
of my own ♪
♪ There'd be new birds ♪
♪ Lots of nice
and friendly ♪
♪ How-de-do birds ♪
♪ Everyone would have
a dozen bluebirds ♪
♪ Within that world
of my own ♪
♪ I could listen ♪
♪ To a babbling brook ♪
♪ And hear a song
that I could understand ♪
♪ I keep wishing ♪
♪ It could be that way ♪
♪ Because my world
would be ♪
♪ A wonderland ♪
[Whistling]
Meow!
Dinah, it'
just a rabbit...
with a waistcoat
and a watch.
I'm late,
I'm late, I'm late!
This is curious.
What could a rabbit
be late for?
Sir!
♪ I'm late, I'm late ♪
♪ For a very
important date ♪
♪ No time to say
"Hello." Good-bye ♪
♪ I'm late,
I'm late, I'm late ♪
It must be important,
like a party
or something.
Mr. Rabbit, wait!
♪ No, no, no, no,
no, no, no. I'm overdue ♪
♪ I'm really in a stew ♪
♪ No time to say
"Good-bye." Hello ♪
♪ I'm late,
I'm late, I'm late ♪
My.
What a peculiar place
to have a party.
Meow.
You know,
we really shouldn't ...
be doing this.
After all,
we haven't ...
been invited.
And curiosity
often leads...
to trouble!
Good-bye, Dinah.
Good-bye-e-e-e!
Oh!
Well, after this,
I shall think nothing--
of falling down stairs.
Oh!
Ah!
Goodness.
What if I should fall...
right through the center
of the ear-r-th...
and come out
the other side...
where people
walk upside down?
But that' silly.
Nobody--oh!
Oh, Mr. Rabbit!
Wait!
Please!
Curiouser and curiouser.
Ohh!
Oh!
I beg your pardon.
Quite all right.
But you did give me
quite a turn.
Rather good, what?
Doorknob...turn.
Please, sir.
One good turn
deserves another.
What can I do
for you?
I'm looking
for a white rabbit.
If you don't mind...
Oh.
There he is!
I must get through.
You're too big.
Simply impassable.
You mean
impossible.
No, impassable.
Nothing' impossible.
Try the bottle
on the table.
Table?
[ Doorknob ]
Read the directions,
and you'll be
directed...
in the right
direction.
Hmm...
Better look first.
For if one drinks from
a bottle marked " poison,"
it' almost certain
to disagree with one.
Beg your pardon?
I was giving myself
some good advice.
But...
mmm...
tastes like...
cherry tart.
Custard.
Pineapple.
Roast turkey.
Goodness!
What did I do?
You almost went out
like a candle.
Look! I'm just
the right size.
Oh. No use.
I forgot
to tell you.
I'm locked.
Oh, no!
But of course,
you've got the key.
Key?
Don't tell me you've
left it up there?
Oh, dear.
Whatever will I do?
Try the box,
naturally.
Oh!
" Eat me."
All right.
Goodness knows
what this will do.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Hmpfh shmf rumph.
What did you say?
A little of that
went a long way.
I don't think
it' funny.
Now I shall
never get home.
Oh, come,
come now.
Crying
won't help.
I know,
but I..I..I
just can't stop.
Say,
this won't do.
It won't do
at all.
You!
You up there.
Stop!
Stop, I say!
Oh, look!
The bottle.
The bot--
Oh, dear.
I wish I hadn't ...
cried so much.
♪ A sailor' life
is the life for me ♪
♪ How I love to sail
o'er the bounding sea ♪
♪ And I never never ever
do a thing about the weather ♪
♪ For the weather never ever
does a thing for me ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ A sailor' life
is the life for me ♪
♪ Tiddlee um pom pom ♪
♪ Deedle dum dum dee ♪
♪ And I never-- ♪
Ahoy!
Another nautical
expression.
Land ho, byJove.
Where away, Dodo?
Dodo?
Three points
to starboard.
Pull away,
me hearties.
Have you in port
in no time.
Mr. Dodo!
Please! Please help me!
Pardon me,
but, uh...
would you mind
helping me, please?
Yoo hoo!
Help me!
Please!
♪ Forward, backward,
inward, outward ♪
♪ Come and join
the chase ♪
♪ Nothing could be drier
than a jolly caucus race ♪
♪ Backward, forward,
outward, inward ♪
♪ Bottom to the top ♪
♪ Never a beginning ♪
♪ There can never
be a stop ♪
♪ To skipping,
hopping, tripping ♪
♪ Fancy free and gay ♪
♪ I started it tomorrow,
but will finish yesterday ♪
♪ Round and round
and round we go ♪
♪ Until forevermore ♪
♪ Once we were behind,
but now we find we are ♪
♪ Forward, backward,
inward, outward ♪
♪ Come and join
the chase ♪
♪ Nothing could be drier
than a jolly caucus race ♪
I say, you'll never
get dry that way.
Get dry?
You have to run
with the others.
But how can I--
Have you dry
in no time.
No one can get dry
this way.
Nonsense.
I'm dry already.
Yes, but--
All right, chaps,
look lively!
The white rabbit.
Mr. Rabbit!
My goodness.
I'm late! I'm late!
I'll be back.
I'm late,
I'm late, I'm late!
Stop kicking
that mackerel.
Mr. Rabbit!
Oh, Mr. Rabbit!
Oh, dear.
I'm sure he came
this way.
Could he be hiding?
Hmm.
Not here.
I wonder...
No. I suppose
he must have--
Why, what peculiar
little figures.
Tweedle Dee
and Tweedle Dum.
Honk!
If you think we're waxworks,
you ought to pay.
If you think we're alive,
you ought to speak to us.
Beep!
Honk!
That' logic!
Well, it' been nice
meeting you.
Good-bye.
You're beginning
backwards.
The first thing
is to say...
♪ " How do you do"
and shake hands ♪
♪ Shake hands ♪
♪ " How do you do"
and shake hands ♪
♪ State your name
and business ♪
That' manners!
Really?
My name is Alice.
I'm following
a white rabbit.
You can't go yet.
The visit is
just started.
Sorry.
Like to play
hide-and-seek...
or who' got
the button?
If you stay long enough,
we might battle.
That' very kind.
But I must be going.
Why?
I'm following
a white rabbit.
I'm curious to know
where he' going.
Oh, she' curious.
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
The oysters
were curious, too.
Aye. And you remember
what happened to them.
Poor things.
Why? What happened
to the oysters?
You wouldn't
be interested.
You're in too much
of a hurry.
Perhaps, I could
spare a little time.
You could? Well...
Beep!
The walrus and
the carpenter.
Or the story
of the curious oysters.
Honk!
Beep! Beep!
♪ The sun was
shining on the sea ♪
♪ Shining
with all its might ♪
♪ He did his
very best to make ♪
♪ The billows
smooth and bright ♪
♪ And this was odd
because it was... ♪
♪ The middle
of the night ♪
♪ The walrus
and the carpenter ♪
♪ Were walking
close at hand ♪
♪ The beach was wide
from side to side ♪
♪ But much
too full of sand ♪
♪ Mr. Walrus,
said the carpenter ♪
♪ My brain
begins to perk ♪
♪ We'll sweep this clear
in 'alf a year ♪
♪ If you don't mind
the work ♪
Work!
Uh...brrrr.
♪ The time has come ♪
The walrus said--
♪ To talk
of other things ♪
♪ Of shoes and ships
and sealing wax ♪
♪ And cabbages
and kings ♪
♪ And why the sea
is boiling hot ♪
♪ And whether
pigs have wings ♪
♪ Calloo, callay,
no work today ♪
♪ We're cabbages
and kings ♪
[Whistling]
Oh...oysters,
come and walk with us.
The day
is warm and bright.
A pleasant walk,
a pleasant talk...
would be
a sheer delight.
Should we get hungry
on the way,
we'll stop
and have a bite.
A-hem.
♪ But mother oyster
winked her eye ♪
♪ And shook
her heavy head ♪
♪ She knew too well ♪
♪ This was no time
to leave her oyster bed ♪
The sea is nice.
Take my advice.
Stay right here.
Mum said.
Yes, yes,
of course...
Ha ha!
♪ The time has come,
my little friends ♪
♪ To talk
of other things ♪
♪ Of shoes and ships
and sealing wax ♪
♪ Of cabbages
and kings ♪
♪ And why the sea
is boiling hot ♪
♪ And, uh...whether
pigs have wings, ho ho ♪
♪ Calloo, callay,
come run away ♪
♪ We're the cabbages
and kings ♪
Uh, hummm...
well, now, uh...
let me see...
A loaf of bread
is what we chiefly need.
How about some
pepper, salt,
and vinegar?
Yes. Splendid idea.
Very good, indeed.
Now...
if you're ready,
oysters, dear...
Ha ha.
We'll begin
the feed!
Feed?
Oh, yes, uh...
♪ The time has come,
my little friends ♪
♪ To talk
of food and things ♪
♪ Of peppercorns
and mustard seed ♪
♪ And other
seasonings ♪
♪ We'll mix them
all together ♪
♪ In a sauce that'
fit for kings ♪
♪ Calloo, callay,
we'll eat today ♪
♪ Like cabbages ♪
♪ And kings ♪
[Whistling]
I, uh...
I weep for you.
[Burp]
Oh, excuse me.
I deeply sympathize,
for I've enjoyed
your company...
much more
than you realize.
Little oysters,
little oysters!
But answer
there came none.
And this was
scarcely odd because...
they'd been eaten,
every one.!
Mmm, well, uh...
Ha ha ha ha.
Mmm, uh...
The time has come--
♪ We're cabbages ♪
♪ And kings ♪
Honk!
Beep!
The end.
That was a sad story.
There'
a moral to it.
A good moral,
if you're an oyster.
It' been very nice.
Another recitation
entitled Father William.!
First verse.
♪ You are Old Father William,
the young man said ♪
♪ And your hair
has become very white ♪
♪ And yet you incessantly
stand on your head ♪
♪ Do you think at your age
it is right, is right? ♪
♪ Do you think
at your age it is right? ♪
♪ Well, in me youth,
Father William replied to his son ♪
♪ I'd do it again
and again and again ♪
♪ And I'd do it again
and again and again... ♪
Now, I wonder
who lives here.
Mary Ann!
Where did
she put them?
Mary Ann!
The rabbit!
No use! Can't wait!
I'm awfully late!
Oh, me, oh, my.
Excuse me.
I'm trying--
Mary Ann,
why are you out here?
Mary Ann?
Don't just do something!
Stand there!
Get my gloves!
I'm late!
Late for what?
My gloves!
At once!
Goodness! I'll be taking
orders from Dinah next.
Hmm...
now, let me see.
If I were a rabbit,
where would I
keep gloves?
Oh, thank you.
Don't mind
if I do.
[Humming]
Ooh!
Oh, no, no!
Not again!
Oh! Mary Ann!
You see here,
Mary Ann.
Help!
[Toot toot]
Ooh! Woo! Ha!
No!
Help! Monster!
Help! Assistance!
[Toot toot]
Oh, dear.
[ White rabbit ]
A monster!
A monster, Dodo!
Dodo?
Steady, old chap.
Can't be as bad
as that.
My poor roof
and rafters!
There it is!
ByJove!
Jolly well is.
Well, do something!
Yes, indeed. Extraordinary
situation, but...
But what?
[Honk honk]
But I have a very
simple solution.
Thank goodness.
Simply pull it out
the chimney.
Pull it out!
Who, me?
Don't be ridiculous.
What we
need is a...
[Whistling]
[ Dodo ]
A lizard with a ladder!
[ White rabbit ]
Oh, Bill! Bill!
We need a lazard
with a lidder.
Can you help us?
At your service,
governor.
Have you ever been
down a chimney?
I've been down
more chimneys--
Excellent,
excellent.
Hop down and pull
that monster out.
Righto, governor.
Monster? Aah!
Oh, no!
Stop!
Wait!
Steady, now!
Aah!
That' better.
You're passing up
a golden opportunity.
I am?
You can be famous.
I can?
In you go, now.
Tie your tail around
the monster' neck...
and drag it out.
But...
but, governor--
Good luck, Bill.
Ah, ah, ah...
ah, ah, ah...
ah, ah, ah, ah, ah...
choo!
Well...
there goes Bill.
Poor Bill.
Uh...perhaps
we should try...
a more energetic
remedy.
Yes!
Anything,
but hurry!
I propose
that we, uh...
Yes?
I propose
that we...
Ooh!
That' it!
We'll burn the house down!
What?
No!
Oh-ho...
♪ Oh, we'll smoke
the blighter out ♪
♪ We'll put
the beast to rout ♪
♪ Some kindling,
a stick or two ♪
♪ Ah, this bit
of rubbish ought to do ♪
♪ We'll smoke
the blighter out ♪
the monster out ♪
No! Not my
beautiful birdhouse!
♪ Oh, we'll roast
the blighter' toes ♪
♪ We'll toast
the bounder' nose ♪
♪Just fetch that gate,
we'll make it clear ♪
♪ That monsters
aren't welcome here ♪
Oh, me, oh, my.
Match.
Match?
♪ Without
a single doubt ♪
♪ We'll smoke
the monster out ♪
the monster-- ♪
No!
My poor house
and furniture!
Dear,
this is serious.
I simply must--
Oh, a garden!
Perhaps if
I ate something,
it would make me
smaller.
Oow!
Help!
I must
eat something.
Not me! You...
you...you barbarian!
Help!
Monster!
Ah! I'm late!
I'm here!
I should be there!
Have a match?
Must go!
Good-bye!
I'm late!
Please wait!
Do you
have a match?
No. Sorry.
Mr. Rabbit!
No cooperation.
No cooperation at all.
Can't have
monsters about.
Have to
carry on alone.
Wait. Please!
Just a minute!
Oh, dear.
I'll never catch him
while I'm this small.
Why...
curious butterflies.
You mean bread
and butterflies.
Of course--mmm?
Now, who do you suppose...
[Whinny]
A horsefly.
I mean, uh...
a rocking horsefly.
Naturally.
I beg your pardon,
but did you...
That' nonsense.
Flowers can't talk.
But of course
we can talk, my dear.
If there' anyone worth
talking to.
Or about.
Ha ha!
We sing, too.
You do?
Let' sing
Tell It To the Tulips.
Or about
shy little violets.
Sing Lovely
Lily of the Valley.
She'd hate it.
Girls! We shall sing
Golden Afternoon.
That' about
all of us.
Sound your " A" , Lily.
♪ La ♪
♪ Mi ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Ah ah ah ah ♪
♪ Dum du dum dum ♪
♪ Poom ♪
♪ Ah-poom mm-hmm
poom oow poom poom ♪
poom oow oow oow ♪
♪ Little bread and butterflies
kiss the tulips ♪
♪ And the sun is like
a toy balloon ♪
♪ Oo-ooo ♪
♪ There are
get-up-in-the-morning glories ♪
♪ In the golden afternoon ♪
♪ Oo-ooo ♪
♪ There are dizzy daffodils
on the hillside ♪
♪ Strings of violets
are all in tune ♪
♪ Tiger lilies
love the dandelions ♪
♪ In the golden afternoon ♪
♪ The golden afternoon ♪
♪ There are
dog and caterpillars ♪
♪ And a copper centipede ♪
♪ Where the lazy daisies ♪
♪ Love the very ♪
♪ Peaceful life ♪
♪ They lead ♪
♪ You can learn a lot
of things from the flowers ♪
♪ For especially
in the month ofJune ♪
♪ Ah ah ah ah ♪
♪ There' a wealth
of happiness and romance ♪
♪ All ♪
♪ In the golden afternoon ♪
♪ All in
the golden afternoon ♪
♪ The golden ♪
♪ Afternoon ♪
♪ You can learn
a lot of things ♪
♪ From the flowers ♪
♪ For especially
in the month ofJune ♪
♪ There' a wealth
of happiness ♪
♪ And romance ♪
[Voice breaks]
♪ All in
the golden afternoon ♪
♪ Ah-ha ♪
♪ Ah ♪
[Crash]
Oh, that was lovely!
Thank you,
my dear.
What garden
are you from?
I don't come
from any garden.
Maybe she'
a wildflower!
I'm not a wildflower.
What specie or genus
are you, my dear?
I suppose you'd call
me a genus humanus Alice.
Ever see an Alice with
a blossom like that?
Did you ever
see an Alice?
Did you notice
her petals?
What a peculiar
color.
And no fragrance.
Just look
at those stems!
Rather scrawny,
I'd say.
I think
she' pretty.
Quiet, Bud.
I'm not a flower!
Just as I suspected!
She' nothing
but a common mobile vulgaris.
Oh, no!
A common what?
To be blunt--
a weed!
I'm not a weed!
She wouldn't admit it.
Can you imagine?
Goodness!
Don't go to seed here!
Go on, now!
Go!
We don't want weeds
in our bed!
Move along!
Toot!
Meoooow!
Arf! Arf! Arf!
All right,
if that' how you feel.
If I were
my right size,
I could pick
each of you!
That'd
teach you.
Ha ha ha ha!
You can learn a lot
from the flowers.
Hmph! They could learn
a lot about manners.
♪ A ♪
♪ E I O U ♪
♪ A E I O U ♪
♪ O ♪
♪ U E I O A ♪
♪ U E I A ♪
♪ A E I O U ♪
Who...
are...
you?
Why, I hardly
know, sir.
I've changed so many times,
you see--
I do not see.
Explain yourself.
I can't explain
myself, sir,
because I'm not
myself, you know.
I do not know.
I can't be clearer.
It isn't
clear to me.
You?
Who are you?
Well, you ought
to tell me--
[Cough cough]
Who...
you are first.
Why?
Oh, dear. Everything
is so confusing.
It is not.
It is to me.
Why?
I can't remember
things as I used to.
Recite.
Hmm?
Oh! Yes, sir.
Um...
how doth the
little busy bee...
improve each--
Stop!
That is not spoken
correcti-cally.
It goes...
how...
Ha ha ha ha.
A-hem.
How doth the little
crocodile...
improve his shining tail...
and pour the waters
of the Nile...
on every golden scale?
How cheer--
A-hem!
Ha ha ha ha.
How cheerfully
he seems to grin.
How neatly
spreads his claws.
And welcomes
little fishes in...
with gently smiling jaws.
I've never heard it
that way before.
I have improved it.
Well...
[Cough cough]
If you ask me--
You?
Who are you?
[Cough cough]
Ah-choo!
Oh!
You there!
Girl!
Wait!
Come back!
I have something
important to say!
Oh, dear.
I wonder what
he wants now.
Oh!
Well?
Keep your temper.
Is that all?
No.
Exacti-cally
what is your problem?
Well,
it' exactic--
Exactic--
It' precisely this.
I'd like
to be larger, sir.
Why?
Well, after all...
3 inches is
a wretched height.
I am exactically
three inches high,
and it' a very
good height indeed!
[ Alice ]
But I'm not used to it,
and you needn't ...
shout!
Oh, dear.
I have some more
helpful hints.
One side makes
you grow taller.
One side of what?
The other side
makes you grow shorter.
of what?
The mushroom,
of course!
Hmm.
One side will
make me grow...
But which is which?
Hmm.
After all that'
happened, I...
I wonder if I...
I don't care.
I'm tired of being
3 inches high.
Yi! Yi! Yi! Yi!
Whoo! Whoo! Whoo!
Ah!
A serpent!
Help! Help!
A serpent! A serpent!
Please, please!
Off with you!
Shoo! Shoo!
Go away! Serpent!
But I'm not
a serpent!
Indeed?
Just what are you?
A little girl.
Little?
Ha! Little?
Ah ha ha ha ha!
Well, I am.
I mean, I was.
I suppose you don't
eat eggs, either.
Yes, I do.
I knew it!
Serpent!
Serpeeeeeeeeent!
Oh, for goodness sake!
And the other side will...
The very idea!
Spend all my time
laying eggs for
serpents like her!
Ahhhhhhhh!
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
Oh!
Goodness.
I wonder if I'll ever
get the knack of it.
There. That'
much better.
Hmm. Better save these.
Now, let' see.
Where was I?
Hmm. I wonder which way
I ought to go.
♪ 'T was... ♪
♪ Brillig and
the slithy toves ♪
♪ Did gyre and
gimbel in the wabe ♪
♪ All mimsy ♪
♪ Were the borogoves ♪
♪ And the momeraths
outgrabe ♪
Now, where do you
suppose that...
Lose something?
Oh! Well, uh...
Ha ha ha.
I-I was...no...
I-I mean...
I-I was wondering...
That' all right.
One moment, please.
Ooh!
Second chorus.
♪ 'T was brillig ♪
♪ And the slithy toves ♪
♪ Did gyre and
gimbel in the wabe ♪
Why...why,
you're a cat.
A Cheshire cat.
♪ All mimsy ♪
♪ Were the borogoves ♪
Oh, wait.
Don't go, please!
There you are.
Third chorus.
I wanted to ask...
which way
I ought to go.
Well, that depends...
on where...
you want to get to.
It really doesn't
matter, as long--
Then...it really
doesn't matter...
which way...you go.
♪ Ah hah, hah hah ♪
♪ All mimsy
were the borogoves ♪
♪ And the momeraths
outgrabe ♪
Oh, by the way...
if you'd really
like to know,
he went...that way.
Who did?
The white rabbit.
He did?
Did what?
Went that way?
Who did?
The white rabbit.
What rabbit?
Didn't you say...
Oh, dear!
Can you stand
on your head?
Oh!
However...
if I were looking
for a white rabbit...
[Clunk]
I'd ask the Mad Hatter.
The Mad Hatter?
No, I don't --
Or...there'
the March Hare...
in that direction.
Thank you.
I shall visit him.
Of course...
he' mad, too.
I don't want to
be with mad people.
Oh, you can't
help that.
Most everyone'
mad here.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
You may
have noticed...
that I'm not
all there myself.
♪ And the momeraths
outgrabe...♪
Goodness. If people
here are like that,
I must try not
to upset them.
How very curious.
♪ If there are
no objections ♪
♪ Let it be unanimous ♪
♪ Oh, a very
merry unbirthday ♪
♪ A very merry
unbirthday ♪
unbirthday to us ♪
♪ A ♪
♪ Very merry
unbirthday to me ♪
♪ To who ♪
♪ Oh, you ♪
♪ A very merry
unbirthday to you ♪
♪ Who, me ♪
♪ Oh, me ♪
♪ Let' all
congratulate us ♪
♪ With another
cup of tea ♪
♪ A very merry
unbirthday ♪
♪ To... ♪
♪ You ♪
[Clap clap clap]
No room!
But there'
plenty of room.
It' rude to sit
without being invited.
It' very, very
rude, indeed!
Very, very, very
rude, indeed.
I'm very sorry.
But I did enjoy
your singing.
You enjoyed
our singing?
Oh, what
a delightful child!
I'm so excited.
We never get
compliments.
You must have
a cup of tea!
Ah, yes, indeed.
You must have
a cup of tea.
I'm sorry I interrupted
your birthday party.
Birthday?
This is not
a birthday party!
Of course not.
This is
an unbirthday party.
Unbirthday?
I'm sorry.
I don't understand.
It' very simple.
30 days have Sept--
No. An unbirthday...
if you have
a birthday, then...
you...
She doesn't know
what an unbirthday is.
How silly!
Ha ha ha ha!
Well, I...
I shall elucidate.
♪ Now statistics prove ♪
♪ Prove that you've
one birthday ♪
♪ Imagine just one
birthday every year ♪
♪ Ah, but there are
364 unbirthdays ♪
♪ Precisely why
we're gathered here to cheer ♪
Then today'
my unbirthday, too.
It is?
What a small world.
In that case...
♪ A very merry unbirthday ♪
♪ To me ♪
♪ To you ♪
♪ A very merry unbirthday ♪
♪ For me ♪
♪ For you ♪
♪ Blow
the candle out ♪
♪ And make your
wish come true ♪
♪ A very merry
unbirthday ♪
♪ To you ♪
Twinkle, twinkle
little bat.
How I wonder
what you're at.
Up above
the world you fly,
Like a tea-tray
in the sky.
That was lovely.
And now, my dear,
you were saying
you were seeking...
Pardon me.
You were seeking
some information of some kind?
Yes. I'm looking
for--
Clean cup!
Move down!
But I haven't
used my cup.
♪ Clean cup,
move down ♪
Would you like
more tea?
I haven't
had any yet,
So I can't take more.
You mean you
can't take less.
You can always take
more than nothing.
But--
And now, my dear,
Something seems
to be troubling you.
Tell us
all about it.
Start at
the beginning.
Yes, yes.
And when you
come to the end...
stop!
It started while
I was sitting...
on the riverbank
with Dinah.
Very interesting.
Who' Dinah?
Dinah' my cat.
Cat?
Cat!
What' got
into him?
Catch him!
Help! Help!
Stop him!
Get the jam!
Put it
on his nose!
C-c-cat...
Ohh...
Oh, my goodness.
Those are the things
that upset me.
See the trouble
you've started?
I didn't think--
If you don't think,
you shouldn't talk.
Clean cup,
move down!
But--
♪ Move down,
move down ♪
♪ Move down ♪
Now, dear,
you were saying?
Oh, yes.
I was sitting
on the riverbank,
with, uh...
you know who.
I do?
I mean my c-a-t.
Tea!
Just a half
a cup.
Come, come, my dear,
don't you care
for tea?
I'm very fond
of tea.
You could
at least make polite conversation.
I've been
trying to ask--
I have an
excellent idea.
Let' change
the subject.
Why is a raven
like a writing desk?
Riddles?
Let me see, now.
Why is a raven...
like a writing desk?
I beg your pardon?
Why is a raven
like a writing desk?
What?
Careful.
She' mad.
It' your
silly riddle.
You just said--
Don't get excited.
A cup of tea?
A cup of tea,
indeed!
I haven't time.
The time!
Who' got the time?
No time,
no time, no time.
Hello. Good-bye.
I'm late! I'm late!
The white rabbit!
I'm so late.
I'm so very late.
No wonder you're late.
This clock is exactly
two days slow.
Two days slow?
Of course you're late.
My goodness.
We'll have
to look into this.
A-ha!
I see what' wrong.
This watch
is full of wheels.
Oh, my poor watch.
Oh, my wheels
and springs.
But-but-but-but...
Butter! Of course!
It needs butter.
Butter!
But-butter?
Butter.
Thank you. Butter.
That' fine.
No, no, no.
You'll get
crumbs in it!
This is good butter.
Tea?
I never
thought of tea.
No! Not tea!
Sugar?
Sugar. Two spoons.
Two spoons.
Thank you.
Be careful!
Jam! I forgot
all about jam.
Mustard!
Mustard, yes.
Mustard?
Don't let'
be silly.
Lemon.
That' different.
That should do it.
[Ring]
Look at that!
Goodness.
Dear.
Mad watch.
Mad watch!
There' only one way
to stop a mad watch.
Two days slow,
that' what it is.
Oh, my watch.
It was?
It was an
unbirthday present.
In that case...
♪ A very merry unbirthday ♪
♪ To ♪
♪ You ♪
Mr. Rabbit!
Oh, Mr. Rabbit!
Now where did he go?
♪ ...to us,
to us ♪
♪ A very merry
unbirthday ♪
♪ To us, to us ♪
Of all the silly nonsense.
This is the stupidest
tea party ever.
I've had
enough nonsense.
I'm going home.
Straight home.
That rabbit.
Who cares where
he' going anyway?
If it hadn't
been for him, I--
" Tulgey Wood."
Hmm. Curious.
I don't remember this.
Now, let me see...
Oh!
No, no, please.
No more nonsense.
Now, if I came
this way,
I should go back
this way.
Honk!
I beg your pardon.
Goodness.
When I get home,
I shall write a book
about this place.
If I ever do get home.
Oh, excuse me!
Could one of you
tell me--
Uh...
never mind.
Caw! Caw!
Oh, dear.
It' getting
dreadfully dark,
and nothing
looks familiar.
I'll be glad
to get out of--oh!
Hoo.
Hoo hoo.
It would be nice...
if something made
sense for a change.
Oh.
The momeraths?
A path!
Oh, thank goodness.
I knew I'd find one
sooner or later.
If I hurry,
I might be home
in time for tea.
Won't Dinah
be happy to see me.
I just can't
wait till I--
Oh, dear.
Now I shall
never get out.
Well...
when one' lost,
I suppose
it' good advice...
to stay
where you are...
until someone
finds you.
But...but who'd ever think
to look for me here?
Good advice.
If I'd listened
earlier,
I wouldn't be here.
But that' just
the trouble with me.
I give myself
very good advice...
♪ But I very seldom
follow it ♪
♪ That explains ♪
♪ The trouble
that I'm always in ♪
♪ Be patient ♪
♪ Is very good advice ♪
♪ But the waiting
makes me curious ♪
♪ And I'd love
the change ♪
♪ Should something
strange ♪
♪ Begin ♪
Well...
I went along
my merry way...
and I never
stopped to reason.
I should have known...
there'd be
a price to pay...
someday.
Someday.
I give myself...
very good advice,
but I very seldom
follow it.
Will I ever learn...
to do the things
I should?
[ Chorus ]
♪ Will I ever learn ♪
♪ Learn to do
the things ♪
♪ I should? ♪
♪ Hmm hmm hmm
hmm hmm ♪
♪ And the momeraths
outgrabe ♪
Oh, Cheshire cat,
it' you!
Whom did you expect?
The white rabbit,
perchance?
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm through
with rabbits.
I want to go home,
but I can't
find my way.
That' because
you have no way.
All ways here,
you see,
are the queen'
ways.
But I've never
met any queen.
You haven't ?
Oh, but you must!
She'll be mad
about you.
Simply mad.
♪ And the momeraths
outgrabe ♪
Please! Please!
How can I find her?
Well,
some go this way,
some go that way,
but as for me,
myself, personally,
I prefer
the shortcut.
Oh!
[ Voices ]
♪ Da dee dee da
da da ♪
♪ Doodle dee do
dee do dee do ♪
♪ Bum ♪
♪ Painting
the roses red ♪
♪ We're painting
♪ We dare not stop
or waste a drop ♪
♪ So let the paint
be spread ♪
♪ We're painting
the roses red ♪
♪ Oh-h-h-h ♪
♪ Painting
the roses red ♪
♪ And many a tear
we shed ♪
♪ Because we know ♪
♪ They'll cease
to grow ♪
♪ In fact, they'll
soon be dead ♪
Oh!
♪ And yet,
we go ahead ♪
♪ Painting
the roses red ♪
♪ Red, red, red, red ♪
♪ Painting
the roses red ♪
♪ We're painting
♪ Oh, pardon me,
but, Mr. Three ♪
♪ Why must you
paint them red? ♪
Huh?
Oh!
The fact is, Miss,
we planted white roses
by mistake.
And...
♪ The queen,
she likes them red ♪
♪ If she saw
white instead ♪
♪ She'd raise
a fuss ♪
♪ And each of us ♪
♪ Would quickly
lose his head ♪
Goodness.
♪ Since this is
the thought we dread ♪
♪ We're painting
the roses red ♪
Oh, dear.
Let me help you.
♪ Painting
the roses red ♪
♪ We're painting
♪ Don't tell the queen
what you have seen ♪
♪ Or say
that' what we said ♪
♪ But we're painting
the roses red ♪
♪ Yes, painting
Not pink.
Not green.
Not aquamarine.
♪ We're painting
the roses red ♪
[Fanfare]
The queen!
[Whistling]
Cards, halt!
Count off!
1 , 2, 3, 4, 5,
6, 7, 8, 9, 1 0,jack!
The rabbit.
Her...
Her Imperial Highness,
Her Grace,
Her Excellency,
Her Royal Majesty,
the Queen of Hearts!
Yea!
Hooray!
And the king.
Hmmm!
Who' been painting
my roses red?
♪ Who dares to taint
with vulgar paint ♪
♪ The royal flower bed? ♪
♪ For painting
my roses red ♪
♪ Someone will
lose his head ♪
Your Majesty,
please.
It' his fault.
Not me,
Your Grace.
The ace!
Two!
Not me!
The trey.
That' enough!
Off with their heads!
Yea!
Hooray!
♪ They're going
to lose their heads ♪
♪ For painting
the roses red ♪
♪ It serves them right,
they planted white ♪
♪ And roses
should be red ♪
♪ Oh, they're going
to lose their heads ♪
Silence!
Oh, please, please.
They were only--
And who is this?
Let me see, my dear.
It isn't a heart.
Is it a club?
It' a little girl.
Yes, and
I was hoping--
Look up.
Speak nicely.
And don't twiddle
your fingers!
Turn out your toes.
Curtsy.
Open your mouth wider,
and always say,
" Yes, Your Majesty!"
Yes, Your Majesty!
Now, where
do you come from?
Where are you going?
I've lost my way.
Your way?
All ways here
are my ways!
Yes, I know.
I was thinking--
Curtsy while
you're thinking.
It saves time.
Yes, but I
wanted to ask--
I'll ask
the questions!
Do you
play croquet?
Why, yes,
Your Majesty.
Then let
the game begin!
[Fanfare]
To your places.
Hurry, hurry!
Shuffle deck!
Cards, cut!
Deal cards!
Cards, halt!
[Squawk squawk]
Silence!
Yea!
Off with his head!
Off with his head.
You heard
what she said.
You're next,
my dear.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Ha ha ha!
Ohh.
Stop!
Of all the
impossible...
You want us both
to lose our heads?
Well, I don't .
Ha ha ha!
Huh?
Ow!
♪ La la la
da da dum ♪
♪ La la la hmm ♪
How are
you getting on?
Not at all.
Beg pardon?
I said, not at all.
Who are you
talking to?
A cat, Your Majesty.
Where?
There!
Oh.
There he is!
I warn you, child.
If I lose my temper,
you lose your head!
We could make her
really angry.
Shall we try?
Oh, no, no!
It' loads of fun.
No, no, stop!
Oh, no!
My fur and whiskers!
Oh, dear!
Save the queen!
Someone' head
will roll for this!
Yours!
Off with her--
Couldn't she
have a trial?
Huh?
First?
Trial?
Well,just
a little trial?
Hmm?
Hmm...
Very well then.
Let the trial begin!
[Fanfare]
Your Majesty...
members of the jury,
loyal subjects...
A-hem.
and the king.
The prisoner is charged
with enticing Her Majesty...
into a game of croquet,
and thereby willfully
teasing, tormenting,
and annoying
our beloved--
Never mind that!
Get to where
I lose my temper.
... thereby causing the
queen to lose her temper.
Now, are you ready
for your sentence?
There must
be a verdict first.
Sentence first!
Verdict afterward.
But that way isn't --
All ways are...
Your ways,
Your Majesty.
Yes, my child.
Off with her--
Consider, we've
called no witnesses.
Couldn't we hear
one or two? Huh?
Oh, very well,
but get on with it!
First witness.
Call the first witness.
The March Hare.
What do you
know about this?
Nothing.
Nothing whatever?
Nothing
whatever!
That' very important!
Jury, write that down.
" Unimportant,"
Your Majesty means.
Silence!
Next witness.
The dormouse.
Well--
Shh!
What have
you to say?
Twinkle, twinkle,
little bat.
How I wonder...
That' the most important
evidence we've heard yet.
Write that down!
Twinkle, twinkle.
What next?
The Mad Hatter.
Oh!
Off with your hat!
Oh, my.
Where were you
when this happened?
I was home
drinking tea.
Today is
my unbirthday.
Why, today is
your unbirthday, too.
It is?
♪ A very merry
unbirthday ♪
♪ To me? ♪
Oh, no.
♪ A very merry
unbirthday ♪
♪ For me? ♪
♪ For you ♪
♪ Now blow the candle
out, my dear ♪
♪ And make
your wish come true ♪
♪ A very merry
unbirthday ♪
♪ To you ♪
Oh! Your Majesty.
Yes, my dear?
There he is now.
Huh? What? Who?
The Cheshire cat.
Cat!
Oh, this
is terrible.
Stop him!
Somebody help me!
Catch him!
The jam!
By order of the king!
Let me have it!
Somebody' head is
going to roll for this!
A-ha!
The mushroom.
Off with her--
Pooh. I'm not
afraid of you.
You're nothing but
a pack of cards.
Rule 42--persons
more than a mile high...
must leave
the court immediately.
I'm not a mile high.
I'm not leaving.
Sorry. Rule 42,
you know.
And as for you,
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
indeed.
Why, you're
not a queen.
You're just
a fat, pompous,
bad-tempered
old ty--
tyrant.
And, uh, what were
you saying, my dear?
She simply said
you're a fat, pompous,
bad-tempered
old tyrant!
Off with her head!
You heard what
Her Majesty said!
Off with her head!
[Fanfare]
♪ Forward, backward,
inward, outward ♪
♪ Here we go again ♪
♪ No one ever loses ♪
♪ And no one
can ever win ♪
♪ Backward, forward,
outward, inward ♪
♪ Bottom to the top... ♪
[ The queen ]
Off with her head!
You can't leave
without having some tea.
I can't stop now.
You must join us
in a cup of tea.
Off with her head!
Mr. Caterpillar,
what will I do?
Who are you?
[Cough cough]
There she goes!
Don't let
her get away!
Off with her head!
Ohh!
Still locked,
you know.
The queen.
I must get out.
But you are outside.
What?
See for yourself.
Why...
why, that' me!
I'm asleep.
Don't let her
get away!
Off with her head!
Alice, wake up.
Alice!
Please
wake up, Alice.
Alice! Alice!
Alice!
Will you pay attention
and recite your lesson?
Hmm? Oh.
How doth
the little crocodile...
improve
his shining tail...
and pour
the waters of--
Alice, what are
you talking about?
Oh, I'm sorry.
You see,
the caterpillar said--
Caterpillar?
Oh, for goodness sake.
Alice, I--
Oh, well.
Come along.
It' time for tea.
[ Chorus ]
♪ Alice ♪
♪ In wonderland ♪
♪ Over the hill ♪
♪ Or here or there ♪
♪ I wonder where ♪
♪ Alice ♪
♪ In Wonderland ♪
♪ How do you get
to Wonderland? ♪
♪ Over the hill
or underland ♪
♪ Orjust behind the tree? ♪
♪ Alice ♪
♪ In Wonderland ♪
♪ Where is the path
to Wonderland? ♪
♪ Over the hill ♪
♪ Or here or there? ♪
♪ I wonder where ♪♪